A Guide to the Papers of W.B. Shafer, Jr. 1939-1981
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Miscellaneous
  - Weil-McLain Model 45 CU-1 Flame Retention Oil Burner, Start Up, Service and Maintenance Manual (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Automobile Related (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Psychics (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Auto-Ramic Banking (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Business Cards (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Booklets (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous and Untitled Contact Lists (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 25)
  - What's My Line? (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Coupons, Stamps, and Products (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 27)
- Artifacts
  - "Thomas Road Tape Ministry" Audiocassette by Jerry Falwell (Box Box 10)
  - Complimentary Refill for your Pallotine Pen (Box Box 10)
  - Box of Buss Auto Fuses (Box Box 10)
  - "Easy Do" Remote Switch (Box Box 10)
  - "Wm. Crooks-Minnesota Pioneer" limited run lithograph (Box Box 10)